# SAGAR SHRESTHA

## • DETAILS •

+977-9860332656 saagarshrest@gmail.com

## LINKS

www.saagarshrest.com

www.dribbble.com/saagarshrest

www.Lottiefiles.com/saagarshrest

www.linkedin.com/in/saagarshrest

#### o SKILLS o

Figma

Interaction Design

Prototyping

Balsamiq

Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Premiere Pro

2D Animation

JSON animation / lottie

Adobe Photoshop

# LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Nepali

#### PROFILE

User Interface/Experience Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Experience of working in domain like FINTECH, EDTECH, HEALTHTECH,FOODTECH & ECOMMERCE, I am Proficient in Figma, Adobe Softwares like XD, Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects, Premier Pro, also softwares like Balsamiq Strong knowledge of aesthetic Designing skills, along with 2D/Lottie Animation.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

## UI/UX Designer at Infinity Digital Agency, Kathmandu

November 2021 — Present

- Gathering data and user requirements based on research and collaboration with client and product managers.
- Creating storyboard, user process flows.
- · Designing wireframes based on UX.
- · Creating high fidelity UI designs.
- Adding Interaction design and prototyping that demonstrates how the design and product functions,
- Identifying and troubleshooting UX problems.

## UI/UX Designer at Dreamax.co.il (Remote), Israel

September 2021 — November 2021

- Conducting User flow research.
- Designing high fidelity UI for platform.
- UX research to create no coding web development builder.
- · Working with developers to solve design issues

## Senior UI/UX Designer at Bitsbeat, Kathmandu

July 2020 — May 2021

- Gathering data and user requirements based on research and collaboration with client and product managers.
- · Creating storyboard, user process flows.
- Designing wireframes based on UX.
- · Creating high fidelity UI designs.
- Adding Interaction design and prototyping that demonstrates how the design and product functions,
- Identifying and troubleshooting UX problems.
- · Conducting training and tutoring interns.
- Guiding juniors in their design process.
- Creating 2D animation for website and videos

#### Designer at Braindigit, Kathmandu

May 2019 — April 2020

• Gathering data and user requirements based on research and collaboration with client and product managers.

- Managing the team to get the job done and create creative content.
- Designing Game UI based on subject requirement.
- Adding Interaction design and prototyping that demonstrates how the design and product functions,
- Identifying and troubleshooting UX problems.
- Conducting training and tutoring interns.
- Guiding juniors in their design process.
- Creating 2D animation for website and videos

# Designer at Floyd Consultancy, Kathmandu

September 2018 — January 2019

- Gathering data and user requirements based on research and collaboration with client and product managers.
- Designing product based on client requirement.
- Guiding juniors in their design process.
- Creating designs for web, mobile and physical product.

#### Designer at Blackspring, Kathmandu

January 2016 — August 2018

- Creating website design.
- · Working with wordpress theme design.
- · Mobile app design.
- · App icon and Logo design.

# EDUCATION

**9** EMBA, Purbanchal University, Kathmandu

# **COURSES**

Ask Question to Make Data Driven Decisions, Google

January 2022

Foundation: Data, Data, Everywhere, Google

June 2021

The Fundamental of Digital Marketing, Google

July 2018

## ■ REFERENCES

References available upon request